Joseph Keppler Jr. Iroquois papers,1882-1944.
Keppler Jr, Joseph, Iroquois papers,1882-1944.
- Series II. Correspondence
  - Wilson, Leroy, 1906 (Box 2, Folder W6.8)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 799
  - Wood, Joseph (Box 2, Folder W7)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 802
  - York, Stephen (Box 2, Folder Y4)
    Also available on Reel 5, Frame 846
- Series III. Other Material
  - Notes given to Kenneth C. Miller Re: Seneca, September 1938 (Box 3, Folder 001)
    Not filmed
  - Joseph Keppler Silver Cross Pendent (Box 3, Folder 002)
  - Acquisition of Keppler Papers (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Also available on Reel 6, Frame 1
  - Ancient rites of the Condoling Council (Mohawk dialect) (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Also available on Reel 6, Frame 10
  - Biographical information about people in calendar section A-P (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Also available on Reel 6, Frame 51
  - Biographical information about people in calendar section Q-Z (Box 3, Folder 3.1)
    Microfilm continued from above.
  - Cayuga notes by Grace Elliot Taft (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Also available on Reel 6, Frame 188
  - Claims: Cauguawagah and St. Regis (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Also available on Reel 6, Frame 202
  - Clippings-Iroquois League (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Also available on Reel 6, Frame 268
  - Clippings-Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Also available on Reel 6, Frame 271
  - Clippings-probably from Joseph Keppler--mostly about Indians of New York State (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Also available on Reel 6, Frame 340
  - Envelopes (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Also available on Reel 6, Frame 356
  - Genealogical information (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Also available on Reel 6, Frame 395
  - Government relations (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Also available on Reel 6, Frame 406
  - Government relations continued (Box 3, Folder 11.1)
  - Government relations continued (Box 3, Folder 11.2)
  - Government relations-Kansas claims (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Also available on Reel 6, Frame 762
  - Government relations-Ryan Thurston Bill (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Also available on Reel 6, Frame 795
  - Government relations-Snell Bill (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Also available on Reel 6, Frame 841
  - Government relations-Vreeland Bill. See also folders 11-11.2 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Also available on Reel 6, Frame 876
  - Handwritten vocabulary notebook attributed to Joseph Keppler (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Also available on Reel 7, Frame 1
  - Handwritten vocabulary attributed to Joseph Keppler (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Also available on Reel 7, Frame 79
  - The Indian as I found him by Cary W. Hartman (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Also available on Reel 7, Frame 131
  - Iroquois masks correspondence (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Also available on Reel 7, Frame 137
  - Johnson, E. Pauline (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Also available on Reel 7, Frame 202
  - Johnson, Evelyn H. C. (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Also available on Reel 7, Frame 274
  - Lacrosse Team (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Also available on Reel 7, Frame 352
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, etc. (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Also available on Reel 7, Frame 356
  - Miscellaneous notes probably by E.K. Burnett (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Also available on Reel 7, Frame 374
  - Miscellaneous vocabulary notes (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Also available on Reel 7, Frame 381
  - New York Indian complex and how to solve it by Arthur C. Parker (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Also available on Reel 7, Frame 429
  - Obituaries (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Also available on Reel 7, Frame 447
  - Indian Tales told by Chauncey Abrams to George G. Heye (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Also available on Reel 7, Frame 467, bound copy not filmed
    Includes 1 bound and one unbound copy of Origin of the Long House, The Woman and the Wolf, Origin of the Moon Dance, The Hunter Who Became a Witch, The Mother and the Twins, and The Man Who Wrestled with the Snake.
  - Our New York Indians, Part II by Erl Bates (Box 3, Folder 29)
    Also available on Reel 7, Frame 477